cuecc.com 2014-02-01

# Privacy Policy of study in china — study in china

.................................................................................................................................................................................... 

## Privacy Policy

Study-in-China, Inc., the operator of this website, (the "Website"), cares about your privacy. This privacy policy details what information is collected and how it is used and applies to visits to or transactions made through this Website.

## Surfing Data

When you visit any page on our Website, we use standard web server log files to collect information on the efficiency and working of our Website. This information includes the number of times a web page is accessed, the browser used, paths taken when moving through the Website, and search terms entered by users. We keep this information for an indefinite time to improve the operation of our Website and to prepare anonymous data compilations regarding traffic on the Website. 

## Collection and Use of Contact Information

We also collect and store personal contact information that can identify you, such as your name and email address, if you voluntarily enter it when requesting information from a school or service. This information passed on to the schools or services you identify (or sometimes to a third party partner or vendor under contract with a school or service you identify) in an email generated by our appointed email address, so that the schools, services or third party partners or vendors may contact you with more information. Other personally identifiable Contact Information may be shared as required to fulfill your information request or to notify you when a third party provides a product or service that we feel may be of interest to you. We may also share your Contact Information with third parties in order that they may send you information relate to you when you have expressly consented to our doing so, such as by clicking a checkbox on our Website. Use of your Contact Information by a school, service or third party is governed by such school's, service's or third party's privacy policy. We will not share your Contact Information with anyone except as provided in this privacy policy. 

## Non-Personal information and Cookies

When you visit and interact with our Website, we may collect non-personal information such as a catalog of the site pages you visit or your IP address. Study-in-China does not use cookies (small files put by some websites on your computer).

## Schools Contacting You

Different schools and services have different methods of following up with student information requests. Some will send brochures in the mail, while others will reply via email or try to contact individuals by telephone. By using our service to request information from schools or services, you are giving permission to the schools or services (or their partners or vendors) to contact you, using the method of their choice, to fulfill your information request.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree to this Privacy Policy, and any changes to the same, by visiting this Website. Therefore, we encourage you to review changes to our privacy policy every time you visit this Website.

## Security

Study-in-China has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your personal information, but cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or relevant Web policies).
